intcomex.com 2019-03-13

# Privacy Policy - Intcomex

Welcome to [www.intcomex.com](http://www.intcomex.com/) and [https://store.intcomex.com](https://store.intcomex.com/), (the “Sites”), these sites are owned by Software Brokers of America, Inc. D/B/A Intcomex, Inc. This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices regarding collection, use and disclosure of information that we may collect from and about you. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information to these Sites. These Sites are intended for use by residents of South America, North America, Central America including Mexico, Caribbean, the United States of America and its territories

* * *

* * *

### Your Consent

By using these Sites, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via these Sites, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Service and any specific provisions of these Sites that may be presented at the time information is collected.

[ Back ]  

### About Children

These Sites are general audience sites. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen on these Sites. If in the future, we collect personally identifiable information from children, we will do so in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.). The Internet offers children wonderful educational and entertainment resources. Your guidance and involvement are essential to help ensure that children have a safe and rewarding online experience. We encourage you to learn more about parental control tools.

[ Back ]  

### Active Information Collection

Like many Web sites, these Sites actively collects information from its visitors both by asking them specific questions and by permitting them to communicate directly with us via e-mail, feedback forms, chat rooms and so forth. Some of the information that you submit may be personally identifiable information (that is, information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your full name, address, e-mail address, phone number and so on). Some areas of these Sites may require you to submit information in order for you to benefit from the specified features (such as newsletter subscriptions, tips/pointers, order processing and so forth) or to participate in a particular activity (such as sweepstakes or other promotions and so forth). You will be informed at each information collection point what information is required and what information is optional.

[ Back ]  

### Passive Information Collection

As you navigate through these Sites and/or receive e-mails in connection with these Sites, certain information may be passively collected (that is, gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies and means, including, without limitation, those described below:

[ Back ]  

### Cookies

As with many Websites, these Sites uses standard technology called “cookies,” which are small data files that are transferred to your computer when you allow your browser to accept cookies. Cookies automatically identify your Web browser whenever you visit these Sites, and make using these Sites easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences. By tracking how and when you use these Sites, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to these Sites are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalize your experience on these Sites. Cookies may also allow these Sites to present to you advertising which may be of interest to you. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, you generally can opt out of providing this information by turning the cookies off in your browser; however, some areas of these Sites may not provide you with a personalized experience if you have disabled the use of cookies.

[ Back ]  

### IP Addresses And Automatic Information

We may collect IP addresses and/or automatic information for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. Our computers identify your computer by its IP address. When you request Web pages from these Sites, our computers log your IP address. Automatic information is information collected by our computers when you request Web pages from these Sites. Automatic information may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at these Sites, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.

[ Back ]  

### Information from other sources

From time to time we, and/or our operational partners may receive information about you from other sources and add it to the data previously collected about you.

[ Back ]  

### Use and Disclosure of Information

Except as otherwise stated, Intcomex, Inc. may use information you provide to improve the content of our Sites, to customize the display of these Sites to your preferences, to communicate information to you (if you have requested it), for our marketing and research purposes, and for the purposes specified in this Privacy Policy.

If you provide personally identifiable information to these Sites, we may combine such information with other actively collected information unless specified otherwise at the point of collection on these Sites. We may combine personally identifiable information with passively collected information.

We may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties located in the United States and/or any other country:

  * to our affiliates;
  * to our sponsors;
  * to other technology related organizations;
  * to select companies or organizations which we believe may offer products, services, materials or information of interest to visitors to these Sites;
  * to third parties we use to support our business (including fulfillment services, technical support, delivery services, chat service providers, e-mail service providers, forum service providers, advertisement sales and management services and financial institutions);
  * in connection with the sale, assignment or other transfer of the business of these Sites to which the information relates; or
  * where required by applicable laws, court orders or government regulations.

In addition, we will make full use of all information acquired through these Sites that is not in personally identifiable form.

[ Back ]  

### Third-Party ad Serving & Audience and Traffic Measurement Services

These Sites may use a third party network advertisers to serve the advertisements on these Sites or may use a traffic measurement service to analyze the traffic on these Sites. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to these Sites and other Web sites you have visited. Third-party ad serving enables us to target advertisements to you for products or Web sites you might be interested in. Although advertisers or other companies do not have access to the Site cookies, the Site’s advertisers, sponsors, and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own cookies on your computer if you choose to have your cookies enabled in your browser. Cookies allow third party advertisers to show you advertisements or content you might be interested in. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Please make the appropriate research in order to learn more about the information collection practices and “opt-out” procedures of third party ad servers we may use.

[ Back ]  

### Access And Correction

To keep your personally identifiable information accurate, current and complete; please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct personally identifiable information in our possession that you have previously submitted via these Sites.

[ Back ]  

### Security

We will take reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information as you transmit your information from your computer to our Site and to protect such information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. In particular, e-mails sent to or from these Sites may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Moreover, where you use passwords, usernames, ID numbers or other special access features on these Sites, it is your responsibility to safeguard them.

[ Back ]  

### Links to Other Web Sites

You should be aware that when you are on the Site you could be directed to other sites beyond our control. For example, if you “click” on a banner advertisement, the “click” may take you off the Site onto a different Web site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use the Site’s logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other Web sites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a Website that is linked to our Site, you should consult that site’s privacy policy before providing any personal information.

[ Back ]  

### Other Terms

Your use of these Sites is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use. If you choose to use these Sites, your visit and any dispute over privacy and data collection is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions of Use including limitations on damages and application of the law of the State of Florida.

[ Back ]  

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of these Sites, please contact us as follows:

Intcomex, Inc.  
Attention: Marketing and Communications Department  
3505 NW 107th Avenue, Doral, FL 33178  
(305) 477-6230

[ Back ]  

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on these Sites. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy was last updated: March/2015.

[ Back ]
